# **OFIR ADATO**

#### **QA TESTER**

@ ofiradatowork@gmail.com

**J** 050-9464923

Holon, Israel

in Ofir Adato

OfirAdato

### **ABOUT ME**

Quality assurance tester, understands and loves the world of testing, Theoretical as well as practical, including writing STP, STD, STR test documents. Practical experience in the testing processes including test management in TestRail, Jira bug reports and STR release. Understanding and experience working with CSS, HTML. Understanding of work processes (Agile).

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **OA TESTER**

### 'CALL-FLOW'

JANUARY 2023 - Ongoing

▼ Tel-Aviv

Quality assurance in the customization department.

### LEVEL B TECHNICIAN

#### 'ONE-TALDOR'

APRIL 2021 - JANUARY 2023

Petah Tiqwa

- A level B technician of ATM machine.
- Technician of computer hardware.

#### FIELD SERVICE TECHNICIAN

### 'BRINKS'

**DEC 2019 - APRIL 2021** 

▼ Tel-Aviv

• Technician of ATM machine.

### MILITARY SERVICE

Signal Corps

march 2017 -nov 2019

Commanders course

- **2018**
- I served as a company sergeant and managed everything related to work arrangements, company tasks.
- Operation of faults in CISCO and JUNIPER routers and switches.

### **PROJECTS**

#### Project 1

https://ofiradato.github.io/html1/

• My profile website

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Quality assurance - Tester
"QA MASTERS"

**JUNE 2022 - October 2022** 

# **SKILLS**

SQL HTML
CSS JAVA

### SOFT SKILLS

Team Work Problem-Solving Responsibility

Self-Learning Strategic Thinking Flexibility

Hard-working Eye for detail

Motivator & Leader

## **LANGUAGES**

# **EDUCATION**

#### "QA MASTERS"

**JUNE 2022 - OCTOBER 2022** 

Thesis title: QA TESTER